Yor is so lucky! This is so unfair!
约尔前辈太狡猾了啦!
I wanted to take a vacation on a luxury cruise too!
我也想搭豪华邮轮去度假!
It's not a vacation. She's entertaining guests for work.
她不是去度假 是去接待客人的
If they needed female staff, they could've chosen me!
需要女性员工的话也可以选我啊!
Apparently, the guest has a baby,
听说那位贵宾有婴儿
so the staff member had to be a mother.
所以要选已经当上母亲的员工
And I guess they're both from the same hometown.
还有 据说她们好像是同乡
At least that's what I heard.
至少我得到的信息是这样
I'm so jealous!
好嫉妒喔!
She's probably enjoying an extravagant dinner,
她现在应该正在享受豪华大餐
eating delicious food!
大快朵颐吧!
Beer and sausages after work isn't so bad either.
下班之后喝啤酒配香肠也不错啊
I agree!
我同意!
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
(远藤达哉原创作品 连载于集英社漫画杂志《SHONEN JUMP PLUS》)
MISSION:31 THE FEARSOME LUXURY CRUISE SHIP
剧名:任务:31 战栗的豪华邮轮
Everything is delicious, isn't it?
这里的餐点很美味吧?
It's prepared by chefs
是巴林特
from a five-star hotel in Berlint.
五星级酒店的主厨料理的
Additionally, local companies supported by the city were used
此外 负责这艘船 零件跟内部装潢的当地公司
for manufacturing parts for the ship, and handling the interior.
也是由市政厅提供支持的
Now, now, let's end this boorish topic.
好了 无聊的话题就不要再继续了吧
Well, I'd like to try dining at that hotel.
希望有机会在那家酒店用晚餐呢
It's delicious.
真好吃
I'm so nervous, I can't taste a thing!
紧张到食不知味了!
Calm down.
冷静点
Enemies won't attack in a public place like this.
敌人不会在这种公开场合攻击
Your family in the third-class cabin can't enter here either.
你的家人在三等舱 也不能进来这里
- You're to entertain the guests for now. - Yes sir.
-你现在就好好接待客人 -是
Why don't we enjoy some drinks at the bar downstairs, Mr. Grey?
要不要到楼下酒吧 喝几杯呢 葛雷先生?
- Sure. - I'll head back to the room.
-当然 -我就直接回房了
Make sure no one is tailing you on your way back.
务必确保回程没有人尾随
I understand.
明白了
No signs of anyone entering while we were out.
没有迹象显示有人入侵
- All right. - In the end, nothing happened all day.
-很好 -结果一整天都没出事
You must not let your guard down.
不可以大意
We don't have proof that your enemies aren't on this ship.
没有证据显示敌人不在船上
There's 30 more hours until we rendezvous with the other ship.
距离跟接应的船会合还有三十小时
If I was the enemy,
假设我是敌人
I would attack right before you're set to leave.
我会选择你准备要离开时动手
No point in causing a scene on a ship when there's nowhere to escape.
根本没必要 在无处可逃的船上引发骚动
Even if our plan hasn't leaked,
就算我们的计划没有走漏风声
there are times when enemies figure things out.
敌人也可能自己猜想到
Tomorrow will be the crucial moment.
明天就是关键时刻
Or so the Director told me!
部长是这么说的!
Let's keep our guard up!
所以还是要提高警觉!
You're right. I'm sorry.
你说得对 抱歉
Maybe I just want to believe that there are no enemies on board.
也许是我自己想相信船上没有敌人吧
This isn't just my problem anymore.
这已经不再是我一个人的问题了
- I have to get my act together. - Yes!
-我得振作起来 -没错!
Once you reach your destination, and your safety is guaranteed,
等到了目的地国家 确保人身安全之后
please let him play outside to his heart's content.
请记得让他在外面玩到高兴为止喔
You really don't seem like you work in the shadows.
你真的不像是黑社会的人耶
I'm sorry! I'll try harder!
对不起 我会加油的!
If we're able to safely make our escape,
如果我们能平安出逃
what will all of you do after that?
你们在那之后要怎么办呢?
If we can't confirm any threats from the enemies, we will stay put.
如果没有发现任何敌人的威胁 我们就待命
We told the other two city hall employees
至于那两位不知情的市政厅员工
that your family will be spending the third day together in private.
我们已经告诉他们 你们在第三天希望没有人打扰
So please don't worry.
所以不用担心
The Director said he will have an excuse for when we disembark.
部长说他会找借口掩护我们下船
What about you? You won't meet up with your family?
那你呢?不去跟你的家人会合吗?
Well... I'm here for work after all...
不...毕竟我是来工作的...
I told them that I'll contact them once I have some time off.
我跟他们说了有空再联系
It seems like this ship will stop at a resort island on the third day.
听说这艘船第三天 会停靠一处度假岛屿
I hope you can spend time there with your family.
希望你到时能跟家人共度快乐的时光
Well... I don't really...
不...我并没有...
Don't overeat just because it's a buffet.
不要因为是自助餐就吃过头了
I played a lot, so I'm hungry.
我玩了好久 肚子好饿
Remember your manners.
注意一下吃相
It's been a while since we had a meal without Mother.
很久没看到母亲在饭桌上缺席了
Yeah. It's lonely without her.
是啊 她不在还真有点寂寞呢
- Father, you're lonesome. - No! I was just agreeing with you.
-父亲你寂寞了 -才没有 我只是响应你说的话
- Finish up, so that we can go back. - These cashews are delicious.
-赶快吃一吃回房间了 -这些腰果好好吃喔
Those were some great drinks, huh, Mr. Grey?
喝得真是尽兴啊 是吧 葛雷先生?
I didn't drink much.
我没喝多少呢
That was an exciting game of darts!
射飞镖的时候 气氛很热烈呢!
You were very skilled, Mr. Grey.
葛雷先生技术很好
- Sorry, I forgot something back there. - What?
-抱歉 我东西忘在那里了 -什么?
Director, you're so clumsy.
部长 您真是冒失
We'll be going ahead.
那我们先走了
There's more to do aside from playing darts.
除了射飞镖 还有很多好玩的
- How about another round of drinks? - No, I've had enough.
-要不要再喝一轮? -不了 我喝够了
Answer my question with a "yes" or a "no".
用“是”或“否”回答我的问题
Are you an assassin hired by Leonardo Hapoon?
你是莱昂纳多哈普派来的杀手吗?
You only have two seconds to answer.
你只有两秒时间作答
I'll break your leg next.
下一次断的就是腿
Are you an assassin hired by Hapoon?
你是哈普派来的杀手吗?
Are there other assassins besides you?
除了你之外还有其他杀手吗?
How many in total?
总共多少人?
Sorry, that wasn't exactly a yes-or-no question, huh?
抱歉 刚刚那不能 用“是”或“否”来回答了吧?
How many are in your team and where are they?
跟你同伙的有几个人? 他们现在在哪?
We're not a team.
我们不是同伙
I don't know how many are on board either.
我也不知道船上有几名杀手
Everyone is working independently. Whoever kills first, gets the money.
大家都是各自行动 先抢先赢
There are some who are selling intel.
还有人是负责贩卖情报
I was tailing you based on the intel I received.
我是根据收到的情报在跟踪你们
Shaty Grey in room 8053.
“8053号房的夏蒂葛雷”
It seems like the intel I received was correct.
看来我收到的情报是正确的
Director, you're back already.
部长 您回来了
What? You're about to soil your pants, Mr. Grey?
什么?葛雷先生 您快拉在裤子上了?
That's not good! Let's rush back to your room.
那真是不妙!我们快回房吧!
Both of you should rest up in preparation for tomorrow.
你们两个也该回房 为明天的工作好好养精蓄锐
Director!
部长先生!
There are numerous assassins on board.
船上已潜入多名杀手
Her name and room number leaked.
她的假名跟房号也都曝光了
The organization had planned this in complete secrecy.
计划是组织以最高机密的方式筹备的
There's no way it could've leaked.
不可能会走漏消息
Do you have any idea how it happened? Did you contact anyone?
你有头绪吗?你有没有联系谁?
No...
没有...
- Did you? - No, the thing is...
-有吗? -没有 我就是...
Three days ago, I made one phone call
三天前 我打过电话
to my parents back home.
给在家乡的父母
You idiot!
愚蠢!
I didn't say anything that would give away this plan. Believe me!
我没有提到 任何会曝光计划的事 真的!
I wanted to say goodbye since I'll never see them again.
是因为再也见不到面了 所以我想打个电话道别
That's all there was to it! I swear!
真的只有这样而已!我发誓!
Enough.
好了
We don't have time to trace our enemy's footsteps.
没时间追查敌人的足迹了
"Whoever kills first, gets the money"?
“先抢先赢”?
I had underestimated things.
是我掉以轻心了
They're not planning to wait until tomorrow to attack!
不用等到明天 他们就要攻过来了!
I don't think we'll go out anymore tonight, so I think I'll get changed.
今晚不会再外出了 我去把洋装换掉
Good idea.
说得也是
Director?
部长先生?
It's room service.
是客房服务
I didn't order anything.
我没有叫啊
You took those darts from the bar?
你拿走了酒吧里的飞镖?
Stop shooting. There's a baby here!
房里有婴儿 请不要乱开枪!
Bring him in the room.
带这家伙进房
- Try not to leave any traces of blood. - Yes sir.
-尽量不要留下血迹 -是
There are numerous enemies on board?
已经有很多敌人上船了?
Our intel has leaked.
情报已经外泄了
We'll leave this room.
必须离开这个房间
There are few rooms in the second-class cabins.
二等舱还有几个空房
Take the three of them and go there right away.
马上带他们三个过去
What about you?
那您呢?
I'll take care of things here, and meet up with you.
我留下来善后 结束之后就去跟你们会合
I understand.
明白了
If we cause a commotion, the ship might turn back.
要是引起骚动的话 船可能会因此返航
In situations where you can't hide the body,
如果遇到无法藏匿尸体的情形
try to avoid fighting all together.
就尽量避免交战
Hide your faces with these masks just in case.
为了以防万一 戴上面具
Hurry.
动作快
Hello. Guest services.
您好 客房服务
Hello. I'm calling from room 8053.
您好 我这边是8053号房
I'm terribly sorry but my wife and I had a big fight,
真的很抱歉 不过我跟我太太刚刚大吵一架
and we damaged the door.
把门给弄坏了 是
Can we ask for a new room?
可以给我们新的房间吗?
I lost contact with Knockman.
我跟诺克曼的联系中断了
Shaty in room 8053
8053号房的夏蒂
is definitely our target.
肯定就是我们要找的目标
The husband's name is listed on the passenger list.
丈夫的名字就在乘客名单上
Including the female voice I heard,
加上我听到的女性声音
there's at least three of them, not counting the baby.
不包括婴儿在内 他们至少有三个人
Is it her bodyguard?
是护卫吗?
They seem to be changing rooms. I'm sure their new room is just a decoy.
看来他们要换房间 新房间肯定是个幌子
Thanks to an impatient somebody, their guard is up now.
都怪有人操之过急 他们现在加强戒备了
If her guard is a member of Garden,
如果她的护卫是花园的人
this won't be an easy task.
这个任务可就没那么简单了
How about we all cooperate together?
大家要不要一起合作?
Of course that means we can't fight among ourselves.
当然那就意味着伙伴之间不能动手
We'll split the reward.
奖金平分
And we will share any information we get our hands on.
拿到情报就随时分享
What a hassle.
那也太麻烦了
It'll be faster if we just kill all the mothers on board with a baby.
直接杀掉船上 所有带着婴儿的女人不是更快吗?
We're assassins, not psychotic murderers.
我们是杀手 不是杀人魔
Our business is built on trust.
我们的生意是以信任为基础
There are few valued clients of The Family on board this ship.
这艘船上还载了许多帮派的大客户
If we want to get paid, we can't cause unnecessary commotion.
想要拿到钱的话 最好不要引起不必要的骚动
As for you, please keep us updated on all that you find out.
至于你 就请你继续更新情报给我们
We're paying you well.
毕竟我们可是付了你不少钱呢
I sell my information impartially.
我的情报是公平贩卖给所有人
Work hard so that you guys don't get outdone by the others.
劝你努力一点 才不会被其他人抢先了
Hey...
喂
Won't these masks make us stand out even more?
这些面具不会让我们更显眼吗?
No worries. There's a masquerade ball being held at the Second Lounge.
不用担心 第二交谊厅刚好在开假面舞会
So please don't remove it.
请绝对不要拿下面具
And please listen to what I'm about to say without turning around.
接下来两位请好好听我说 千万不要回头
I believe we're being followed.
我们也许已经被跟踪了
Ever since we left the room.
从我们离开房间开始
No way. What are we going to do?
不是吧 那我们该怎么办?
Let's lose him before they find out our destination.
在他们察觉我们的目的地前甩掉他
Will we be able to do that?
没问题吧?
Heading towards the stern. Probably going to the Second Lounge.
往船尾移动中 很可能是要前往第二交谊厅
Okay. We'll head there.
好 我们往那里过去
We're here.
到了
Bloodthirst!
杀气!
They're coming! While we're in this crowd!
来了!居然在人群中...
If I intercept and kill them, it'll cause a scene.
截杀敌人的话会引起骚动的
Then the rendezvous might get canceled.
那么跟接应船会合的事情 也会被迫中止
Hey.
喂
Excuse me.
抱歉了
I can't kill anyone.
我不能杀人
They sensed our presence.
他们察觉到我们的存在了
But they don't know where we're stationed.
不过我们的位置没有曝光
I can kill her. I'll just pass by, and prick her with this poison.
我能干掉她 只要擦身而过时 用这根毒针戳一下就可以了
I'll end it in a flash...
瞬间就能搞定...
Sir, you've had one too many drinks.
客人 您喝太多了
That was close.
真是好险
Huh? What was close? Give me my button.
什么?什么好险?把钮扣还我啊!
What? What just happened?
什么?发生了什么事?
Sir.
客人
Hey Andre! They're entering the lounge!
安德烈 他们要进交谊厅了!
Don't lose them! The black-haired woman is their guard!
别跟丢了! 黑发女人就是他们的护卫!
Find a blind spot and aim for the blonde.
以金发女人为目标 找死角下手
Roger.
收到
Oh... my...
喔 天啊
Are you asking me to dance with you?
您是想邀请我共舞吗?
I'm sorry, but I'm not a very good dancer.
抱歉 可是我很不擅长跳舞呢
Plus...
而且...
Believe it or not, I'm a married woman.
别看我这样 我已经结婚了
So I can't accept your offer.
所以不能接受您的邀约
- Good day. - Andre! What happened?
-失陪了 -安德烈 你怎么了?
Please rest for a little while.
请您稍微休息一下
Andre! Answer me!
安德烈 回答我啊!
We were able to lose them. Hurry, let's go downstairs.
终于甩掉他们了 我们赶快下楼
Past the promenade are the second-class cabins.
穿过购物大道之后就是二等舱了
DECK 4 SHOPPING PROMENADE
(第四层甲板 购物街)
Father! I want this skeleton keychain!
父亲 阿尼亚想要这个骷髅钥匙扣!
It's so unnecessary. Why is that even sold on board?
有够多余的 船上为什么连这个都卖?
- I want it, I want it! - It's late. Let's return to our room.
-人家想要... -时候不走了 回房间吧
I want it, I want it!
人家想要...
There are bugs placed all over this ship.
船上到处都是监听器
There are many government elites and celebrities here,
毕竟船上有这么多政商名流
so I'm sure there are few from the State Security Service on board too.
船上肯定有几个是安全部的人
I spotted a few suspicious people in addition to the State Security members.
除了安全部人员 我也注意到几个可疑人士
I'll lay low, and try to stay out of the way.
我还是低调点 别跟他们扯上关系
- I want it, I want it! - So much for laying low...
-人家想要... -低调点...
- He should just buy it for her. - How cute.
-就买给她嘛 -真可爱
Oh crap! This conversation is being heard too!
糟了 这段对话也会被他们听见!
A normal parent would just buy it for their kid! You must be a spy!
一般正常的父母亲都会买给小孩吧 可疑的家伙 你一定是间谍!
You asshole! We're arresting you!
人渣 我们要逮捕你!
Which is it? Would a parent normally buy it or not?
买还是不买? 一般的父亲到底会不会买?
This is obviously unnecessary!
可是这怎么看都很没必要啊!
It's not good for her education either!
对她的教育也没有半点帮助!
But if I make one wrong choice, it could mean my life!
但要是选错了 代价可能是我的命!
I don't want it after all.
我想想还是不要了
I'll kill them.
杀了他们
Did he really tell us to not cause a commotion? I don't care about that.
要我们不要引起骚动?关我屁事
It's 400,000 dalc for that woman and her damn child.
女人跟臭小鬼加起来就有40万达克
I won't let those sissy assassins take them from me!
我才不要让给那些光说不练的杀手!
I'm the Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby.
我锁链手巴纳比
I never fail to kill my target.
从来没有失手过
Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby! Who is that?
锁链手巴纳比...那是谁?
There they are.
来了啊
According to the intel I intercepted,
根据我拦截到的情报
the black-haired woman is the skilled guard.
黑发女人是很厉害的护卫
I'll kill her first.
就先解决那个女人
Mother!
母亲!
That assassin is trying to battle with Mother right here, right now!
那个杀手要跟母亲在这里展开战斗
Should I buy it or not?
到底该不该买?
Take this! Sickle-and chain frog!
接招吧 吃我的锁链蛙!
I hate frogs!
我讨厌青蛙!
What's happening?
怎么了?
Yor? You're an assassin that hates frogs?
约...约尔小姐 原来你是个讨厌青蛙的杀手?
Let's split. No more Forger family.
离婚吧 没有福杰一家了
We'll dump Anya too!
阿尼亚也不要了!
Oh no! What should I do?
惨啦!我该怎么办?
I'm sorry, Anya.
是我不对 阿尼亚
Let's buy this skeleton.
我们去买这个骷髅吧
It'll be a precious memento of our cruise trip.
它会是这趟邮轮之旅的重要回忆
A normal father. A good father.
一般的父亲 好父亲
I don't care about that! Go away!
那种东西不重要啦!你别过来!
At this rate, Mother's battle will begin any time now!
再这样下去 母亲随时就要展开战斗了!
I'll buy it for you, so please don't get mad. Okay?
我买给你就是了 别生气了 好吗?
If I let Father walk out of this store, he'll see Mother fighting!
要是让父亲走出这家店 就会看到母亲在战斗!
Oh no! It's a battle!
糟啦 有人在战斗!
What's happening? What? Yor, you're part of this battle?
怎么了?什么? 约尔小姐参与了这场战斗?
Once he hears any screaming, it'll be the end!
要是被父亲听到尖叫声也会完蛋!
I'm the one that wanted to take this cruise, so I have to do something!
是阿尼亚自己想搭船的 所以阿尼亚要想想办法!
What's with that face? Is she sad? Mad?
这表情是怎么了? 是难过?还是生气?
What is she feeling right now?
她现在到底是什么心情?
Did I hurt her that much by refusing to buy that skeleton?
只是拒绝买骷髅而已 就这么伤她的心吗?
Are kids this age emotionally unstable?
这个年纪的小孩情绪都这么不稳定?
That's right. You learned this a while back, Twilight.
对了 这点你老早就知道了啊 黄昏
She may be trying to conceal it,
也许她很拼命在压抑
but there's constant darkness in her heart!
但她心中的黑暗仍然不曾散去!
- Her wound never healed! - Um...
-她心中的伤不曾痊愈! -那个...
Caring for Anya's needs is a part of Operation Strix.
照顾阿尼亚小妹妹的需求 也是“枭”行动的一环
Handler was aware of this all along?
管理官早就看清这一切了?
That's why she planned this mission in the name of a family trip to create peace!
所以她为了创造和平 才以家庭旅行为由计划了这次任务!
I will complete this mission!
我一定会完成任务!
Father is always off the mark.
父亲每次都搞错重点
Excuse me, are you looking for anything in particular?
不好意思 两位在找什么商品吗?
Lately, these t-shirts and hoodies with our logo are popular.
最近这种有我们商标的 T恤跟连帽卫衣很红
Neckties with a whale design are popular with fathers.
爸爸的话 可以挑这条有鲸鱼图案的领带
How about matching baseball hats for the two of you?
要不要买亲子帽呢?
There is a fitting room over there. Please try it out.
更衣室就在那边 可以去试试看喔
No, we're not looking for that...
不了 我们没有在找那些...
I've no time for this. I have to look after Anya's mental state.
没时间管这个了 我得照顾好阿尼亚的心理状态
- Father, you don't get it at all. - Huh?
-父亲你根本就不懂 -什么?
An adventure is about enjoying a type of excitement out of the norm.
冒险就是要享受与平常不同的兴奋感
Out of overwhelming excitement,
因为好兴奋
one starts to want skeletons and wooden swords.
才会想要骷髅或是木剑
Father, you're not excited at all!
父亲根本就不兴奋!
If you're like that, it makes me feel down too.
这样的话 阿尼亚也会提不起劲
I think you should express your excitement
为了让阿尼亚更加享受这趟旅行
with your entire being, in order to please Anya!
你应该全力表现出兴奋感 !
She's right.
她是对的
I'm Twilight, the man with 1,000 faces. How could I have forgotten?
我黄昏明明拥有千变万化的脸孔 怎么会忘了这一点?
It's important to play the role!
重要的是要投入角色扮演
I must be a fun, and cheerful father!
扮演一个有趣又愉快的父亲
Miss, I'd like to try on those clothes.
店员小姐 我想试穿那些衣服
- In fact, I'll wear it back to my room. - Okay!
-而且我要直接穿回去 -好的
Father, those pants over there with the squid print look fun!
父亲 那件有鱿鱼图案的裤子 看起来很好玩
I will try on every single article of clothing in this store.
请让我试穿店内所有服饰
I understand. This way.
好的 这边请
I'll be expecting to see a very fun outfit.
我想看到很好玩的打扮
Leave it up to me.
交给我吧
Please let me know if you need a different size.
需要其他尺寸的话 请跟我说一声喔
All right! Let's keep Father in there for a while and buy some time!
很好 这样就能把父亲困在这里 争取一些时间了!
In the meantime, I have to help Mother!
我要趁现在去帮母亲!
Oh crap!
糟了!
I forgot that Father is a master of disguise!
我忘了父亲是变装大师!
He can change clothes in seconds!
换衣服不过几秒钟的事!
I don't understand!
我不明白!
These clothes don't go well together at all!
这些衣服根本就不搭!
Is this the way to go? How am I supposed to express excitement with my outfit?
这样对吗?我要怎么用服装 展现出我的兴奋?
Is there an optimal solution?
有最佳解答吗?
Dammit! This is no good. I need to search for an even more perfect outfit!
可恶 这样不行 我得找出更加完美的打扮!
What? They're not going to start fighting?
什么?还没有开始打吗?
She dodged that?
竟然躲开了?
All the while protecting the other two...
而且同时还保护了其他两个人...
I didn't sense his hostility until the last second!
我直到最后一秒才感觉到杀气!
This man...
这个人...
is strong!
很强!
NEXT X MISSION
(下一项任务)
MISSION:32 WHO IS THIS MISSION FOR?
(任务:32 为了谁的任务)
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita
字幕翻译:洪贞韵